So I just want to say I feel good about the Republican Party.
I feel good about where we're going as a nation.
We're killing all the right people and we're cutting your taxes.
Is there systemic racism in this country in policing and in other institutions?
No, not in my opinion.
Trump is my favorite president.
We've run out of bombs.
We didn't run out of bombs in World War II.
Were we wrong to drop an atomic bomb to end the Japanese reign of terror?
Were we?
I'm not with you.
I'm with Israel.
I'll be with Israel to our dying day.
You just wait for Cuba.
Cuba is a communist dictatorship that's killed priests and nuns.
They preyed on their own people.
Their days are numbered.
America first is to kill people who wish us ill to take them off the table.
When this regime goes down, we're going to have a new Mideast.
We're going to make a ton of money.
You just wait to see what comes in the next two weeks.
The next two weeks meaning what?
We're going to blow the hell out of these people.
The mothership of international terrorism is about to collapse.
We're going to move your city forhlint.
We're going to argue for steel and running nous.
The mothership of international violence, you have to make love for the Germans for erupיו.